Do you think Mossad is a force for good
or not?
>> Well, they serve Israel's interests,
which is uh not the same thing as
America's interests at all. And on the
topic of Iran's nuclear program, for
example, they forged what was purported
to be an Iranian scientist's so-called
smoking laptop back in the W. Bush
years, and they pretended that this
laptop proved that Iran had a secret
nuclear weapons program. And all of it
was eventually debunked, but it helped
heighten the risk of war between Iran
and the United States over this alleged
nuclear weapons threat. And as we talked
about on the show last week, Pierce,
Iran has a latent nuclear capability.
They've proven that they've mastered the
fuel cycle. But the Ayatollah has said
he doesn't want nuclear weapons and
America's intelligence agencies and
Israel's intelligence agencies have
continually reaffirmed that they have
not made the decision and changed that
decision. Essentially, I think the
consensus is among the reasonable
experts on this is that if we don't
threaten them and especially if we don't
attack them, then they're not going to
make nukes. If we do attack them, they
might. and they're saying essentially if
you don't attack us we won't. So it's a
standoff and we could leave it at that.
I mean they have mastered the fuel cycle
literally 20 years ago in 2005 they
started spinning these centrifuges and
proving that they can enrich uranium 235
and so I'm not saying the Ayatollah is
the most responsible player in the world
or anything like that but it's clearly
heightening tensions against them which
increases the threat that they would
then make the decision to break out
toward a nuclear weapon and then we
would have Israel lead the United States
into another disastrous war in the
Middle East.
Alan Dwitz, you're shaking your head
there.
>> Well, should Israel really trust and
depend on the possibility that maybe
Iran is not going to develop a nuclear
weapon? Just two days ago, Ayatollah
Kamani said he was determined to destroy
uh Israel. Rafson Johnny, the former
liberal head of Iran, said if Iran
develops a nuclear bomb and drops it on
Tel Aiv, it will kill 3 million Jews.
And Israel is a onebomb state. It will
end Israel. Israel will then retaliate
and drop a bomb on Tehran. It will kill
10 million Muslims. Uh but the trade-off
will be worth it because it will be end
of the Zionist entity and Islam would
still survive. Life is always a question
of probabilities and possibilities. And
in my new book, The Preventive State, I
go through all the options that
governments have to try to prevent
likely, sometimes even unlikely
scenarios and and the CIA uh as well as
the Mossad are there to minimize uh the
likelihood of devastating experiences.
You ask if if a Mossad is good or if
it's evil. I actually defended uh two
young men who were arrested, Mossad
agents in Cyprus back in the 1990s. And
I got a letter from the former head of
the Mossad, the man who preceded the
guest. And here's the way he ended the
letter. And this how it tells you
everything you need to know. May we all
live to see the day when a profession
such as mine gives way to more pleasant
occupations.
Still there is there is still some time
and a way to go before this comes about.
Look, we know the Mossad is necessary.
The question of whether it's good, evil,
intermediate, those are matters of
degree and opinion. But the idea that
Israel uh one of the smallest nations
and the most hated nations in the world,
one of the most frequently attacked
nations, attacked since even before it
was established, could do without the
Mossad is preposterous. The Mossad saves
lives, Israeli lives, American lives,
European lives. It prevents terrorism.
And like all intelligence agencies, it
does things we wish it didn't have to
do. As the former head of the Mossad
said, we hope for a day when that
profession is not necessary, but
tragically we're not even close to that.
So, two and a half cheers for Mossad. It
does a great job. It's more like the CIA
than it is like any other intelligence
agency. And on balance, it does a great
deal of good, not only for Israel, but
for the world.
>> I mean, Alan, Alan, the Israeli
historian.
>> Yeah. I mean, like the whole notion that
Iran has these nuclear weapons that
they're going to threaten the entire
world with is absolutely pathetic and
laughable. Um
whether they have the technology or not,
by the way, nuclear technology so old
that was so 1930s. I mean, um there's
reports now where Russia has similar
bombs that could create the same damage
and I think Iran has them too without
the um using without the radiation and
all that crap. So the nuclear weapons
thing is just uh um an excuse for the
Israelis to conduct a regime change in
Iran. Whether they have them or not, you
know, it doesn't make a difference. The
Israelis have uh nuclear weapons
themselves illegally, by the way,
stolen. And we can go into details on
how it was stolen on a a ship route
that was targeted by a unit 8200 MSAD
that literally stopped a ship in route
to uh sending nuclear bombs to Europe to
France actually uh where they eventually
stole
uh a certain amount of nuclear warheads.
So they're a de facto undeclared nuclear
state. And so the fact that they have
been propagandizing this whole thing
that Iran's developing ballistic
missiles and they're going to launch
them towards America. Well, okay, so
does North Korea, so does Pakistan.
And they claim that these these are some
host some of the most dangerous
terrorists in the world. And so far
they've
for the most part at least been um able
to contain themselves from launching a
nuclear weapon towards America because
they know that will be the end of their
their entity as well. So it's a big
hoax, right? And you know, Alan Dersitz,
who constantly defends the genocide
going on in Gaza, he he'll sit there and
try to justify that, oh, Mossad is
necessary and Mossad are these great
players defending Jewish people all over
the world. Well, yeah. And they're also
blackmailing
um all our politicians through a sex
rank, you know, that was headed by
Epstein. So, there's that, too. Um, also
they have been uh involved in a few
other things that we're not going to get
into uh too much detail about, but just
think of major events that have occurred
the past 30 years.
>> An author and politician Michael Barzoha
said of the Mossad, "The dirtiest action
should be carried out by the most honest
men." Um, you know, does the end justify
the means to you? You're a very very
highprofile and very highly reputed
lawyer. Are you comfortable with the way
that the Mossad has conducted itself
over the decades from a legal
perspective or sometimes is it justified
for the Mossad to behave illegally if
the ends justify the means?
Now, everybody knows how much I enjoy my
tea and I'm very happy to say trusted
>> the ends are and what the means are. If
the Mossad could have prevented the
Holocaust, if it could have prevented
October 7th, if it could have prevented
some of the other devastating events,
the killing of so many American Marines
in the barracks in Lebanon, then you
might say yes, uh the means, even if
they sometimes exceeded the limits of
acceptable law, would be justified. If
not, I mean, your previous guest talked
about the Mossad forging a laptop, but
then they went in and they discovered
that in fact the Iranians, although they
had promised and had a fatwa against
having developed nuclear weapons, were
developing uh nuclear weapons all the
time that they promised, they they
weren't. So,
>> that's not true at all.
>> The ends don't generally justify the the
the means depending on the means. But
when the means are calibrated and when
the ends are cataclysmic, uh you
sometimes need to take the kind of
preventive action that we wish we
wouldn't have to take. We don't live in
a perfect world. We live in a world that
has had holocausts and genocides and all
kinds of horrible things to the extent
these can be prevented uh by largely
legal activities. And remember, the vast
majority of what the Mossad does just
looks up things. and goes into public
and open sources and tries to get the
best conceivable intelligence it can.
But it also has to engage in terrible
actions. Yes, it has to kill people who
have killed Israelis in order to send a
deterrent message. After the terrible
Munich massacres, Golden Mayer said
every single person who was involved in
killing Israeli athletes will be killed.
And the Mossad did it and they made one
mistake. They killed one innocent
person. That's typical of the way
intelligence services operate. Mostly
they do preventive action. Mostly they
do good and sometimes they overdo it and
sometimes they make mistakes. That's why
we have the rule of law.
>> Okay. John Keryaki, you said this. Um we
saw this is the CIA when you were there.
We saw what the Israelis were getting
away with in these prisons that they had
in the West Bank and in Gaza. Nobody
raised any objection at all. So, we
thought, well, if the Israelis can do
it, we can do it. The president said we
could, and the justice department said
we could, and so we did. You've also
separately described Mossad uh saying
that it has a negative,
disproportionate, and widespread
influence on the US national security
state. So, you're clearly not a fan of
the MOSAD. Why?
>> Well, the the job of really any
traditional intelligence service is to
recruit spies to steal secrets. And
that's great because every country's
leaders need those secrets in order to
form the best possible policy. But when
the secrets are being stolen from the
US, the major US defense contractors,
from Capitol Hill, from the US
intelligence uh community, from the
State Department, there there's a
problem there. I remember when I first
joined the CIA and this is going back 35
years. There was a declared Mossad
officer in the Israeli embassy and a
declared Shinbet officer and the FBI was
able to identify
187 additional Israeli intelligence
officers at work in the United States
clandestinly.
I would say why why would they steal
secrets when we give them 99%
of everything that we already have?
But doesn't the United States steal
secrets from Israel, too? Of course they
do.
>> No, actually, no. The the Israelis were
off limits to us at the CIA. We were not
permitted.
>> I don't believe that for I don't believe
that. I don't believe that for one
second. I have information definitely
that the United States has stolen
secrets. I know it for a fact and I
don't think you can credibly dispute
that.
Well, you know,
Go ahead.
Well, Jeff Stein, the great uh
Intelligence Beat reporter from
Newsweek, uh would report every year on
an intelligence report that the FBI
would put out about the worst counter
intelligence threats in the United
States. And it was Russia, China, and
Israel. And eventually what happened was
it it caused such a scandal after time
after time of this coming out that Diane
Feinstein ended up changing the rules so
that they didn't have to issue the
report anymore. So that Jeff Stein
wouldn't be able to report on it
anymore. But they were uh alleged by the
FBI counter intelligence division to be
the most damaging spies in America only
after our supposed adversaries Russia
and China.
>> In fact, at the CIA
Well, hang on, hang on, hang hang on one
second. I want to ask Danny actually
because you you ran Mossad, you know,
did did Mossad steal secrets from the
CIA, for example?
As far as it was published,
nowadays no. The answer is no.
Probably it was the situation until the
polar defair. Once the polar affair
happened and it
became a big crisis that influenced to
the worst the situation the relations
between Israel and the United States the
Mossad stopped working on an American
soil. On the contrary, I don't know if
you know, but there are very very close
and intimate relations between Mossad
and CIA and between Shinbet and FBI and
we are working together. We are sharing
information
and as a matter of fact our best ally is
the United States and our best ally
to the Mossad is the CIA.
>> John I want to come to you about
something that you stated which is that
you believe that Jeffrey Epstein was a
Mossad agent.
>> I believe that he was an Israeli access
agent. You know if if a foreign
intelligence agency wants information
from very highly placed from very
important sources. They they're not
going to be able to recruit those
sources directly. So, you recruit
somebody who has access to those
sources. And I think that that's most
likely uh what Jeffrey Epstein was.
>> You knew Jeffrey Epstein.
>> Yeah. By the way, you know, when they
talk about how MSAD wasn't this uh the
greatest ally the CIA has and stuff,
several CIA agents have come out and
said, you know, the the horrible
experience they've had dealing with
them. Uh, one CIA agent in particular
was talking about how they used to um,
you know, try and recruit agents that
worked in the CIA, right? Uh, that look
Jewish. They would go up and try and
recruit them so they could spy on uh,
the CIA and they would they would come
and give a lot of the officials gifts
and stuff like that. They would
all the time be wiretapped and and u
there'll be a wire in there listening
devices and they plant that everywhere
they can get into. So it's like a they
do have that relationship but they're
constantly the CIA and the FBI are
constantly being sabotaged by these same
individuals. And we're going to get into
how Epstein was a tool to also blackmail
uh high-ranking politicians, executives,
you name it, right into doing into
making sure that whoever's in office
continues to maintain the the
pro-Israeli policies that have been
going on for such a long time.
>> I was in Israel writing a book and one
day Jeffrey Epstein called me. I was his
lawyer and he said, "I've never been to
Israel. Uh, I'd like to come there and
meet some people. Can you get a lunch
together for me with six of Israel's
smartest people?" And so I arranged a
lunch in the Tel Aiv Hotel at which the
president of the Supreme Court, the dean
of this, the dean of that. He didn't
know any Israelis. He absolutely didn't
know anybody. I took him on a trip to
the shook. We bought a couple of
surveyors. He got on the plane that
night.
>> He got he knew I had Barack afterward as
a matter of they did business uh
together, but not when he was the prime
minister at all. And and and the idea
that the Mossad would retain somebody
like Epstein is just preposterous.
Epstein uh was what he is, but he was
not a Mossad agent. And and the idea is
so conspiratorial and so absurd. It just
focuses on because Epstein is famous and
infamous. Oh, Israel must have something
to do because it's Jewish. At bottom,
it's a core anti-semitic notion. If
you're Jewish, you must have some
connection with Israel and you must be
doing bad things and you must be a spy
for Israel. It is so preposterous, so
absurd. Epste was many things, but he
was not. On the contrary,
>> if if I were a Mossad uh officer, I
would have targeted him from my first
day on the job because he had access to
people then would have been absolutely
not
>> important people with important
information.
>> You are dealing with fake information.
>> Well, let's go to somebody who may know
the answer for sure. Danny.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. Talk to us about Jeffrey. Remember,
I I reiterate what I said
some 15 minutes ago. Since the
Polar affair,
we do not dare to do anything
related to espionage in the United
States of America.
>> Weren't you the guy that tapped Bill
Clinton's phone?
>> I know Clinton very well because I met
him the president. I'm so glad he
mentioned that because the reason Polard
was released is because they had a phone
sex tape between Clinton and Lewinsky
that was set to be released. Um, unless
he stopped the whole two-state solution
that he was trying to have Arafat and
Ravine sign and
the uh and also released Jonathan Polard
who was convicted for spying on high
ranking American officials. He was
working for the American government, was
convicted on spying for Israel.
And um yeah, so I'm so glad this guy
just mentioned that. Holy [__]
>> Clinton, because I met him a lot of
times when I was the chief of staff of
Barack and participated in all the
rounds of talks with the Syrians,
Palestinians, Jordanians, and the
Americans. I was part of the of the
group being in Cam David. I know him
very very well. I appreciate very very
well President Clinton and I think that
he
as all the other presidents as well
assisted
essentially the state of Israel. You
have to understand we are a small
country. We are surrounded by enemies.
Till now all the terror organizations
are
with the aim to kill as many Israelis
and as many Americans by the way as
possible. The Iranians call us the
little Satan and you they call the big
Satan. So we need to have very good and
professional intelligence apparatuses.
>> Okay. But Danny, let me ask you. Danny,
let me ask you something. Danny, let me
just jump in.
>> Yes.
>> Danny, let me ask you something. As a as
a former head of MOSAD, if Jeffrey
Epstein had been working with Mossad,
would you even tell us? Would you admit
it?
>> Exactly. So, how do we know? As I
understand,
as far as you have to believe. How do
you know that there is God?
>> He just said you wouldn't tell me.
>> If you believe God exists. Yeah. It is a
question of belief. Either you believe
me or
>> you just told me you wouldn't tell me if
he had
>> I speak.
>> I did not meet I did not abain ever.
>> I know him.
>> I don't know him. Sorry. I don't know
him. I don't think inense.
Let me give you a fact. Let me give you
a fact. Okay. Let me ask Alan
>> because it was a talking over each other
again.
>> I'm going to make
>> Hang on. Hang on, please. Everyone's
talking again. Hang on. Alan. Alan. Let
me ask you a Allan. Let me ask you a
question. Alan, let me let me ask you a
question. Have you ever worked with
Mossad?
>> Yes, I represented Mossad to help get
two people out of Cyprus. I did it pro
bono and I got this letter from the head
of the Mossad thanking me uh for doing
it. Let me tell you another thing. I was
Jeffrey Epstein's lawyer. I know
everything about him. If he had worked
for the Mossad, he would have told me
that and I would have used it as a way
of trying to reduce his sentence. He
didn't tell me that. He told me nothing
like that. So there's no way in which he
worked for the Mossad and didn't tell me
that he worked for the Mossad because I
could have used that to get him an even
shorter sentence than the one he got.
There is no possibility that he did
that. Of course, I'm so proud of the
fact that I helped to get two people
out. Let me tell you what happened. They
were arrested by Cyprus on the theory
that they were working as spies for
Turkey. Those were the days when Turkey
was close to Israel. I was able to prove
that in fact they were there in order to
prevent a an attack from terrorists on
Israeli people who were coming as
tourists and sailing their boats there.
As soon as I was able to persuade the
criate authorities that that was the
case, they freed them and that was a
wonderful moment. They came home in time
for Russashana for the Jewish holiday.
>> All right, those guys are just going to
keep on babbling guys. But um anyways,
yeah, I mean, look, man, there there's
just so much mounting evidence to
suggest that Epstein was involved with
Mossad uh from and I think Scott Horn
was about to mention this, uh him dating
Robert Maxwell's daughter, Drizzling,
right, who uh he was a prominent MSAD
figure and was uh uh literally she was
saying that he would uh impose sexual
intercourse with her and uh do all types
of creepy [__]
And so there's that connection and then
there's also who Barack who would
constantly be on at Epstein's house, you
know, giving him the blueprint as to who
to target and which American officials
to go for, Donald Trump being one of
them. Uh there's also the uh the Lex
Wexter connection who funded his
Victoria Secret mansion.
um the $77 million pedophile mansion and
and there's so many connections that
that just and look if if you were MSAD
or if I were MSAD and this [__]
who knows all the American officials and
by the way all these spy agencies all
these intelligence agencies spy on each
other and it's it's normal right whether
they're allies or not they have to know
what's going on. So, um,
there's that. And then there's there's
all these CIA agents coming out saying
like, "Yeah, these guys used to give us
gifts on during Christmas and they'd
have listening devices and everything."
And, uh, I think the UK prime minister
said that Netanyahu snuck a listening
device, uh, while he, you know, where he
was going to when he was using the
restroom, you know, like he he he snuck
it on his toilet and this guy Netanyah
Na was like listening to the guy taking
shits and stuff. So, uh, yeah, bro.
There's just too much mounting evidence,
uh, to suggest that there was the
connection there, um,
and that, you know, all these people
were working together to blackmail as
many people as they can. And then, um,
also the other guy, one of the the
former MSAD heads said, "Oh, um, well,
no, after the Jonathan Polar situation,
we stopped doing espionage on the United
States." Okay. Yeah. Well, how did you
release Jonathan Polard? He was
released. We know now because they
threat literally threatened Bill Clinton
with a phone sex tape that they were
supposed to release if if Polar wasn't
released and that he sabotaged the
two-state solution agreement, you know.
So, um, and they eventually even, you
know, released some information that
Lewinsky, who who was herself also
involved with the Mossad,
um, was given Bill Clinton's some head
some, you know, heady under the table.
People are wondering why didn't Hillary
ever leave Bill Clinton? I mean, the
guy, you know,
and she knows what's up. She knows that
it was just some [__] blackmail
going on, you know. So, um, yeah, man.
It's just and again it's just this is
the whole manipul and even if the guy
knew he's not going to tell us on air
you know.
So yeah, just interesting interesting um
way they like to twist their